Chris Huynh

Santa Ana, CA 92707 ceewizzhuhwin@gmail.com – 949-414-2130 SUMMARY

A hard-working **Computer Software Engineering** student at Cal State Fullerton with a background in marketing and **Full Stack Web Developer**. Attended the coding boot camp at the University of California Irvine earning my certificate in full-stack web development. An open-minded outgoing team player who possesses great problem-solving skills and is always up for challenge an awesome ability with great troubleshooting and good interpersonal. Over 4 years of business marketing and customer service experience. A patient critical thinker who remains calm in high-stress situations with well-developed people skills. A desire to accomplish success at what I do.

GITHUB: https://github.com.ceewizz

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/chris-huynh-8ba0b5291/

Portfolio: https://chrisreactportfolio-8c9aa6f3e388.herokuapp.com/

Technical / Front-end skills Acquired

HTML5, CSS, Javascript, API Designs (Client-Server Model, API, Rest, JSON, AJAX, HTTP request methods, GraphQL), GIT, Bootstrap, C++, C#

• Quality Assurance (Unit Testing, Linting, Continuous Integration)

Performance Back-end SKILLS ACQUIRED

- -NODE JS, O.O.P, EXPRESS, NOSQL, PROGRESSIVE WEB APPLICATIONS(PWA)
- MONGO, MONGOOSE, REACT, MEARN STATE.
- -ADVANCE KNOWLEDGE IN PC, MAC, AND MOBILE ELECTRONIC DEVICES
- -PCB COMPONENT REPAIR AND ADVANCE MICRO SOLDERING SKILLS

- -STRONG KNOWLEDGE OF VIRUSES APPLICATION GLITCHES AND HARDWARE ISSUES.
- -EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION AND PROBLEM SOLVING SKILLS
- WELL FOCUSED, AND PROACTIVE, VALID DRIVER LICENSE, ABLE TO LIFT UP TO 70LB
- -KEEPS ABREAST OF CHANGES IN TECHNOLOGY, PROFICIENT TROUBLESHOOTER
- -GOOD ORGANIZATIONAL ABILITIES, INVENTORY MANAGEMENT
- -GOOD UNDERSTANDING OF INSTALLATIONS AND UPDATES, DIVERSE PC KNOWLEDGE

Projects/Work

Game Bargains: https://game-bargains.onrender.com/

This project is a video game app that searches for savings based on the top 60 games with the highest Metacritic scores of the week. The user can view game info, "favorite" games on sale, and keep track of prices with their wish list.

Password Generator:

https://ceewizz.github.io/PasswordGen/

A Password Generator using JavaScript that enables employees to generate random passwords based on criteria that they've selected.

Video Vault:

https://video-vault-a9fdebd79a00.herokuapp.com/

-The motivation behind this project was to test our knowledge of what we've learned throughout the course and to culminate it into a full-stack web application. We were able to build a full-stack application using our knowledge of Javascript, SQL, Node, Sequelize, Express-session, and cookies. The project that we created is called VideoVault, it's a full-stack web application that stores links of video, as well as images from multiple social media

Coding Quiz:

https://ceewizz.github.io/CodeQuiz

Commented [CH1]:

- A timed quiz on JavaScript fundamentals that stores high scores SO THAT I can gauge my progress compared to my peers.

Progressive Web Applications (PWA Text Editor):

https://pwatexteditor-cwz-e3c67fb4c29e.herokuapp.com/

- Progressive Web Applications (PWA) Challenge: Text Editor As you have progressed through this course, you have put together a number of impressive projects that you can show off to potential employers. This project is no exception; in fact, it features some of the most impressive expressions of the concepts you have learned so far.

EXPERIENCE

"UBREAKIFIX" & "QWIK Wireless" APPLE / PC / Mobile Electronics Repair Technician / IT Engineering Support - Santa Ana, CA - 2009-09 - 2017-05

- Level I & II Apple iPhone, iPad, Tablet, and Advanced Super AMOLED Glass Lens Separation Procedures Liquid Damage Restoration/Advanced Level III Board Level Repairs and Component Testing.
 - Advanced Level III Techniques for Soldered/Heat Transfer Surface Mounted Components
 - Business Operation and Marketing Strategies along with Wholesale Suppliers.
- Accumulate the most benefits and trust for company/store by providing consistent quality repairs with warranty to make sure we earn satisfaction from every single customers.

Business Marketing/Finance

WORLD FINANCIAL GROUP - Fountain Valley, CA - 2008-06 - 2009-08

- Assisting clients with their financial problems, presenting benefits and differences in close comparison between each company
- Help clients with investments, insurance, 401k benefits, and presenting to them why it is so beneficial in the long run, and how their interests multiply.

TECHNICIAN FOR MOBILE ELECTRONICS "QWIK WIRELESS", Westminster, CA October 2015 -

BUSINESS SALES/MANAGEMENT

VECTOR CUTCO INC - Costa Mesa, CA - 2008-10 - 2009-05

Costa Mesa, CA October 2009 - Jan 2012

- Introducing products through one on one presentations
- Providing details and forever warranty on products
- Persuasive skills on completing 95% of sales
- Top 5 in the whole company across the country to bring back the most successful presentations and money for the company in the shortest about of time and was awarded with a Certificate and a Letter of Recommendation along with many gifts from the President of the company.

Tech Representative

TEL PHIL, INC - Costa Mesa, CA - 2008-01 - 2009-01

- Collaborated with a team in the Parking Department to maintain the park program such as guiding the customer to available parking spots.
- Responsible for the money collection at the cash boxes.
- Handled and resolved customer's problems. Always made the customer satisfied about the parking issues.

Manager

O.C FAIR. PARKING DEPARMENT - Costa Mesa, CA - 2008-06 - 2008-08

- Supervised a team of 15 people to maintain the parking program for two parking lots.
- Controlled vehicles coming in and out the fair to make sure there was not any issue with the traffic. Collaborated with other teams to resolve any issues during the fair.

Cashier/Customer Service

TASTEA, INC - Westminster, CA - 2007-09 - 2007-12

- Quickly handle customers orders, kept busy line moving fast, maintained and organize workspace following safety standards
- Handled cashier counters to maintain correct cash flow in the crowed store.
- Worked in high stress environment to meet customer needs.

EDUCATION

A.A. in Computer Science

Orange Coast College 2011-05

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

- Computer Software Engineer- California State Fullerton (CSUF)
- Full Stack Web Development- University California Irvine (UCI)

AWARDS

Outstanding Academic Excellence

2004-06

Awarded by the President of the United States George W bush for outstanding academic excellence.

Vector INC, CEO Award

2011-05

Being in one of the 5 business sales marketing people to successful help bring in the most profit to the company in the least amount of time

Math/science medal

2004-02

Silver medal for 2nd place in the whole school District in the Math/Science competition Bronze medal for 3rd place in the state in the Math competition.